SOFTWARE ARCHITECT · SECURITY EXPERT

42-8, Bangbae-ro 15-gil, Seocho-gu, Seoul, 00681, Rep. of KOREA

[(+82) 10-9030-1843 | ■ posquit0.bj@gmail.com | 😭 www.posquit0.com | 🖸 posquit0 | 🛅 posquit0

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary_

A self-motivated developer with 2+ years of experience in a fast-paced leading educational startup and continuously striving to expand skill sets. Proficient in Python/Django and learning new programming languages like Golang. Aspiring to be part of a team that solves problems using technology and learn new things. Have a bachelor's degree in Computer Science.

Experience _____

Entri.me Ernakulam, Kerala

PRODUCT ENGINEER Feb. 2015 - Present

Feb.n2015 the insignate employees

- · Designed a payment processing system and integrated with Payumoney and Razorpay for processing the payments
- Integrated with SendGrid for transactional emails and Mvaayoo for transactional SMS
- Designed and implemented REST APIs to support entri.me Android Application
- Developed responsive web applications with Bootstrap and Sass preprocessor
- Created dashboard to track and analyse student performance for teachers

Recursive Labs Ernakulam, Kerala

SOFTWARE TRAINEE March. 2014 - Jan. 2015

Febsed & ND/FSFOX Operating System from day 1 and did Python based projects and programming assignments.

· Gained exposure in developing web applications using Python based frameworks like Django and Flask

Honors & Awards

INTERNATIONAL

| 2018 | Finalist, DEFCON 26th CTF Hacking Competition World Final | Las Vegas, U.S.A |
|------|---|------------------|
| 2017 | Finalist, DEFCON 25th CTF Hacking Competition World Final | Las Vegas, U.S.A |
| 2014 | Finalist, DEFCON 22nd CTF Hacking Competition World Final | Las Vegas, U.S.A |
| 2013 | Finalist, DEFCON 21st CTF Hacking Competition World Final | Las Vegas, U.S.A |
| 2011 | Finalist, DEFCON 19th CTF Hacking Competition World Final | Las Vegas, U.S.A |

DOMESTIC

| 2015 | 3rd Place, WITHCON Hacking Competition Final | Seoul, S.Korea |
|------|--|----------------|
| 2017 | Silver Prize, KISA HDCON Hacking Competition Final | Seoul, S.Korea |
| 2013 | Silver Prize, KISA HDCON Hacking Competition Final | Seoul, S.Korea |

Presentation

DevFest Seoul by Google Developer Group Korea

Seoul, S.Korea

PRESENTER FOR < HOSTING WEB APPLICATION FOR FREE UTILIZING GITHUB, NETLIFY AND CLOUDFLARE>

Nov. 2017

- Introduced the history of web technology and the JAM stack which is for the modern web application development.
- Introduced how to freely host the web application with high performance utilizing global CDN services.

6th CodeEngn (Reverse Engineering Conference)

Seoul, S.Korea

PRESENTER FOR < DEFCON 20TH: THE WAY TO GO TO LAS VEGAS>

Jul. 2012

• Introduced CTF(Capture the Flag) hacking competition and advanced techniques and strategy for CTF

Writing_

March 2, 2021 Byungjin Park · Résumé

FOUNDER & WRITER Jan. 2015 - PRESENT

• Drafted daily news for developers in Korea about IT technologies, issues about start-up.

Program Committees

2016 **Problem Writer**, 2016 CODEGATE Hacking Competition World Final

S.Korea

2013 Organizer & Co-director, 1st POSTECH Hackathon

S.Korea

Education

Lourdes Matha College of Science and Technology

Kerala University

B.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering

Mar. 2009 - 2013

• Organised inter college computer science fest

Extracurricular Activity

PoApper (Developers' Network of POSTECH)

Pohang, S.Korea

CORE MEMBER & PRESIDENT AT 2013

Jun. 2010 - Jun. 2017

- Reformed the society focusing on software engineering and building network on and off campus.
- Proposed various marketing and network activities to raise awareness.

PLUS (Laboratory for UNIX Security in POSTECH)

Pohang, S.Korea

MEMBER

Sep. 2010 - Oct. 2011

- · Gained expertise in hacking & security areas, especially about internal of operating system based on UNIX and several exploit techniques.
- Participated on several hacking competition and won a good award.
- · Conducted periodic security checks on overall IT system as a member of POSTECH CERT.
- Conducted penetration testing commissioned by national agency and corporation.